[
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "か",
    "back": "ka",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ア",
    "back": "a",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "イ",
    "back": "i",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ウ",
    "back": "u",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "エ",
    "back": "e",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "オ",
    "back": "o",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "カ",
    "back": "ka",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "キ",
    "back": "ki",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ク",
    "back": "ku",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ケ",
    "back": "ke",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "コ",
    "back": "ko",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "サ",
    "back": "sa",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "シ",
    "back": "shi",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ス",
    "back": "su",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "セ",
    "back": "se",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ソ",
    "back": "so",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "タ",
    "back": "ta",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "チ",
    "back": "chi",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ツ",
    "back": "tsu",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "テ",
    "back": "te",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ト",
    "back": "to",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ナ",
    "back": "na",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ニ",
    "back": "ni",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ヌ",
    "back": "nu",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ネ",
    "back": "ne",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ノ",
    "back": "no",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ハ",
    "back": "ha",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ヒ",
    "back": "hi",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "フ",
    "back": "fu",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ヘ",
    "back": "he",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ホ",
    "back": "ho",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "マ",
    "back": "ma",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ミ",
    "back": "mi",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ム",
    "back": "mu",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "メ",
    "back": "me",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "モ",
    "back": "mo",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ヤ",
    "back": "ya",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ユ",
    "back": "yu",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ヨ",
    "back": "yo",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ラ",
    "back": "ra",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "リ",
    "back": "ri",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ル",
    "back": "ru",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "レ",
    "back": "re",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ロ",
    "back": "ro",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ワ",
    "back": "wa",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ヲ",
    "back": "wo",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "Katakana",
    "front": "ン",
    "back": "n",
    "started": false,
    "reviewDay": ""
  }
]
